# Wing Ho Cheung

Hello, this is Sam, an international student studying at Seneca College.

Richmond Hill, ON

wingho19960707@gmail.com

Hong Kong Baptist University graduate with professional background in video post-production and customer service, as well as having 3 years media production and a year customer service working experiences. I build up an outstanding interpersonal and practical skills from the above experiences.

I am an international student holding a Study Permit and looking for a part-time job offer.

### Work Experience

#### **Registration Officer**

Immigration Department - Hong Kong February 2021 to July 2021

- Processing Applications relating to Hong Kong Identity Card matters
- Customer Service
- General Clerical Support

#### **Customer Service Executive**

HKT Services Limited - Hong Kong January 2020 to December 2020

- Handle general enquiries, billing enquiries and complaints
- Cooperate with other teams members to resolve customer's request
- Promote company products and services

#### **Senior Digital Media Production Officer**

TFI Digital Media - Hong Kong October 2016 to June 2019

- Live Streaming event to social media platforms
- Video Editing for promo and event archives
- Video Transcoding in different streaming formats for OTT platforms

#### Education

#### DCS / DEC in Computer Programming

Seneca College - Markham, ON September 2021 to Present

#### DCS / DEC in Post-production (Editing and Sound Mixing)

Hong Kong Baptist University - Hong Kong

September 2014 to July 2016

### Skills

- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- Open Broadcaster Software
- Photography

## Languages

- Cantonese Advanced
- English Intermediate
- Mandarin Intermediate
- Chinese Fluent